Here's how Vince Staples flipped Kobe
Bryant's jersey numbers into a brilliant
double on Tandra.
>> 32 [music]
pop it when I'm lonely
at the same throwing [music] 20s on her
back like she
>> along with signing a specific model of
Glock. 32 is what you get when you add
the two jersey numbers Kobe wore 24 and
8, hence both Kobes. Fittingly, Kobe
entered the NBA in the 9697 season, the
same year the Glock 32 was introduced.
The basketball gun analogy continues.
Pop it when I'm lonely. With pop here
referencing a gunshot and the nickname
of Greg Papovic, legendary coach of the
Spurs, hence the reference to Spurs
player Monty Gernobi in the next line.
Meanwhile, at the Sams refers to Sam's
Hoffbrow, an LA strip club just three
miles [music] from where the Lakers
play. So, Vince is describing throwing
$20 bills while getting a lap dance, and
the 20's fall on her back, the same
place Gobbley wore the number 20 on his
jersey. If you like this breakdown,
check out my new episode that dissects
the most mind-blowing number schemes in
rap